

# Arman Ajabkhani

SENIOR JAVA DEVELOPER - BACK END

### **PROFILE**

Gender: Male Nationality: Iranian Birth Date: 8/25/1983

I am a software engineer with more than 10 years'experience in software developing with Several roles including developer, designer, technical team lead in various projects. Concentration, high interaction with teammates, responsibility and perseverance, key observations in operational environments and issue solving are my main characteristics. Learning new concepts, distributed systems and Software Quality(functional and nonfunctional) are interesting and exciting for me.

# **EDUCATION**

**Bachelor of Science** from Sheikh Bahaee Isfahan University in Software Engineering from September 2000 to September 2006.

# **LANGUAGES**

English

Persian

## **CONTACT**

Email: arm.khani@gmail.com Mobile: +98 912 8589 456

LinkedIn: Arman Ajabkhani's profile

Address: No. 23, Parastoo2 Alley, Kaj St.,

Taherkhani St., Tehran, Iran

### WORK EXPERIENCE

# *SNAPP*(ride sharing)

# Senior Java Developer

July 2019 - Present

My responsibility as a senior java developer.

- I developed reactive java using RxJava and Vert.x and Swagger.
- Responsible for designing and development of multiple services implementing Microservices.
- I design and implement feature in user account and notification implementing Microservices.

# Sava Arman Kish(Crypto-currencies Exchange)

# Senior Java Developer

Nov 2018 - Jul 2019

My responsibility as a senior java developer.

- I developed reactive java using RxJava and Vert.x and Swagger.
- Responsible for designing and development of multiple services implementing Microservices.
- I design and implement feature in user account and notification implementing Microservices.

# TOSAN(Payment and Banking solution provider)

# Senior Java Developer /Team Lead

Nov 2011 -Nov 2018

- Mentoring, coaching, training and planning tasks for the team members.
- Analysis, Design, Development, Deployment and

Maintenance several applications and micro-services.

- Designing and developing some complicated features in open banking API.
- I worked as a member of the Channel Manger (CM) team.
- $\hbox{-} I \ developed \ functional ities for \ tracking \ and \ authentication \ and \ authorization.$
- I developed and implemented Web Services with JAX-WS.
- I implemented many feature in Persistence layer using Hibernate
- I had Extensive experience using framework APIs like spring and Hibernate.

### Elm o Sanat

# Senior C#/ASP.NET Developer

Sep 2010 -Oct 2011

- I implement several new features in the School product.
- I used Entity Framework in school product and custom report generator.
- I implement virtual replication on SQL Server with use web service.

# *Netbina (Online Advertising)*

# Junior C#/ASP.NET Developer

October 2006 -March 2009

- I implemented several functionalities for the advertising products.
- I work on developing a Blog Service with C# and ASP.NET.



# Arman Ajabkhani

SENIOR JAVA DEVELOPER - BACK END

# PROGRAMMING SKILLS

| Java / JVM                            | Spring                       |
|---------------------------------------|------------------------------|
| SOA/Micro-services                    | Spring Boot                  |
| Test Driven Development               | Spring MVC                   |
| Event Driven Architecture             | Spring Security              |
| Software Architecture Patterns        | Spring Cloud                 |
| Design Patterns                       | Spring Batch                 |
| Live Migration                        | Spring Data / JPA/ Hibernate |
| Concurrent Programming                | Spring AOP / aspectj         |
| Reactive Programming                  | Vert.x / RxJava              |
| RESTful Web Services                  | Redis / Redisson             |
| SOAP / JAX-WS /JAX-RS                 | Oracle                       |
| Docker                                | MySQL / SQL Server           |
| OpenShift                             | Gradle / Maven               |
| Jenkins/Gitlab CI/CD                  | Swagger UI/ Codegen          |
| Financial / Banking / Payment Systems | Git / Subversion / TFS       |
| Crypto Currency Exchanges             | ActiveMQ/ Rabbit MQ          |
| UML / Agile and RUP Methodologies     | Apache Tomcat                |
| Confluence / SharePoint / Documenting | OAuth / JWT                  |
| Jira / TFS / HP ALM                   | JUnit / TestNg / Mockito     |
| Scrum                                 | <u>C</u> #                   |
| Distributed Systems                   | <i>ETEX</i>                  |